mammothmountain.com 2017-06-22

# About | Mammoth Resorts

**Terms and Conditions**

Welcome to the websites of Mammoth Resorts (including, without limitation, mammothmountain.com, snowsummit.com, bearmountain.com, bigbearmountainresort.com, junemountain.com, cali4niapass.com). Mammoth Mountain Ski Area, LLC, Snow Summit, LLC, and their affiliates ("Mammoth Resorts", "we", "us", or "our") provide these websites to you (collectively, the “Sites”), subject to the following Terms of Use ("Terms of Use"), which  govern your use of any of our websites containing a link to these Terms of Use, and subject to our Privacy Policy, which is incorporated into these Terms of Use by this reference.  Please read these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy carefully before using our Sites. By using any of our Sites, you agree to these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use and the Privacy Policy, you should not use our Sites or the services we provide on them.

Privacy Policy

By agreeing to the Terms of Use, you agree to the terms of our Privacy Policy, which is expressly incorporated into these Terms of Use. All personal data provided to us as a result of your use of these Sites will be handled in accordance with our Privacy Policy.

License to Use Our Sites

As long as you are in compliance with the terms of this Agreement and all associated documents incorporated herein, Mammoth Resorts hereby grants you a limited, revocable, non-assignable, non-sub-licensable, non-exclusive license to access the Sites via an ordinary Internet browser, to view the Sites and all information and materials, including but not limited to the Materials, as defined herein. The Agreement impacts your legal rights and responsibilities and should be read carefully.  Any violation of the terms or conditions of this Agreement is grounds for immediate termination of this limited license. No other rights are granted, implied or otherwise.

Important Notices and Additional Terms and Agreements

The Sites may contain typographical errors or inaccuracies, including but not limited to errors or inaccuracies related to price, product information, service information, product description or availability, and may not be complete or current. Mammoth Resorts reserves the right to correct any errors, inaccuracies or omissions (including after any order has been submitted, confirmed and/or charged to your credit card) and to change or update information at any time without prior notice. Please note that such errors, inaccuracies or omissions may relate to pricing and availability, and we reserve the right to cancel or refuse to accept any order placed based on incorrect pricing or availability information.

We have made every effort to display as accurately and reliably as possible the colors, sizes, dimensions, materials, textures, and all other physical aspects (“Depiction”) of the goods, services or locations that may appear on the Website.  However, we cannot guarantee, and make no warranty, promise, or agreement that any depicted or described product, service or location actually comports with its Depiction or description.

Any price quotation, service information or any other such information regarding the provision of and fees for any goods or service offered by Mammoth Resorts or the benefits of employment with Mammoth Resorts are provided purely for informational and illustrative purposes. Mammoth Resorts does not guarantee, and makes no warranty, promise, or agreement that any depicted or described goods or services are actually offered or comports with its description on the Website. Mammoth Resorts reserves the right to cease offering any such goods, services or benefits to any prospective or actual employee or customer at any time, in all cases without notice or liability.

We may also require you to follow additional rules or guidelines in order to sign up to use various special features or password-protected areas of our Sites, to make purchases or reservations on our Sites, to participate in certain promotions available through our Sites, or for other reasons. In such cases, you may be asked to expressly consent to additional terms, for example, by checking a box or clicking on a button marked “I agree.” This type of agreement is known as a “click-through” agreement. If any of the terms of a click-through agreement are different than the terms of these Terms of Use, the terms of the click-through agreement will supplement or amend these Terms of Use, but only with respect to the matters governed by the click-through agreement. In addition, certain policies or terms of sale may apply to online purchases or reservations made on our Sites, which may deemed accepted when you complete or confirm your purchase or reservation. All additional terms and click-through agreements as described in this paragraph are referred to as “Additional Terms.”

Mammoth Resorts Content

Our Sites contain text, graphics, video, audio, or other content provided by Mammoth Resorts or its partners (collectively, “Mammoth Resorts Content”) and such content is protected under applicable intellectual property laws.  All Mammoth Resorts Content and related intellectual property rights are the property of Mammoth Resorts or the material is included with the permission of the rights. Mammoth Resorts grants you permission and license to lawfully access and use these Sites and to display, print, or download one copy of the Mammoth Resorts Content on any single computer for your personal, noncommercial use only, provided that you (a) do not modify the Mammoth Resorts Content; (b) you retain any and all copyright and other proprietary notices contained in the Mammoth Resorts Content; and (c) you do not copy, post, distribute or transmit the Mammoth Resorts Content on any other website, via any network computer or broadcast the Mammoth Resorts Content in any media.

You expressly recognize and agree that Mammoth Resorts' trademarks, including our resort and hotel names and logos (the "Mammoth Resorts Marks") are the sole property of Mammoth Resorts. You are not authorized to display or use the Mammoth Resorts Marks or the trademarks, product names, company names, logos, service marks and/or trade dress of any other owners featured on our Sites without the prior written permission of the owner.

Any applicable software you may download from or access on our Sites, including any files, images, or data accompanying the software (collectively, the "Software") are licensed to you by Mammoth Resorts for the limited use described in the preceding paragraph. Mammoth Resorts transfers no right, title or interest in the Software to you. Mammoth Resorts retains full and complete title to the Software, and all intellectual property rights therein. You may not redistribute, sell, decode, reverse engineer, disassemble, or otherwise reduce the Software to a human-perceivable form.

Content You Submit to the Sites

Some of our Sites may provide you with the ability to add, create, upload, submit, distribute, post, or share on or through the Site, content, including without limitation information, website links, opinions, photos, profiles, graphics, videos, and audio clips (“User Content”). 

By posting any User Content on the Site, you expressly grant, and represent and warrant that you have the right to grant, to Mammoth Resorts a non-exclusive, irrevocable, worldwide, transferable, royalty-free, perpetual license to publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, distribute, create derivative works, and sublicense your User Content in any manner or through any media now known or later developed without any payment to you. 

Mammoth Resorts may choose, in its sole discretion, to pre-screen, edit, refuse, move or remove any User Content posted to the sites. You agree that exercise of that discretion by Mammoth Resorts does not convert the User Content into Mammoth Resorts Content.

Conduct

You agree to not use the Sites to:

  * upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any User Content that is unlawful, harmful, threatening, abusive, harassing, tortious, defamatory, vulgar, obscene, offensive, libelous, invasive of another's privacy, hateful, or racially, ethnically or otherwise objectionable;
  * engage in or facilitate harassing conduct aimed at any other person or entity;
  * harm minors in any way;
  * impersonate any person or entity or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
  * forge headers or otherwise manipulate identifiers in order to disguise the origin of any content transmitted through the Sites;
  * upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any User Content that you do not have a right to transmit under any law or under contractual or fiduciary relationships (such as inside information, proprietary and confidential information learned or disclosed as part of employment relationships or under nondisclosure agreements);
  * upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any User Content that infringes any patent, trademark, trade secret, copyright or other proprietary rights of any party;
  * upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any unsolicited or unauthorized advertising, promotional materials, "junk mail," "spam," "chain letters," "pyramid schemes," or any other form of solicitation;
  * upload, post, e-mail or otherwise transmit any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;
  * interfere with or disrupt the Sites or servers or networks connected to the Sites, or disobey any requirements, procedures, policies or regulations of networks connected to the Sites;
  * ·violate any applicable local, state, national or international law, and any regulations having the force of law.

Copyright Infringement Complaints

Mammoth Resorts respects the intellectual property of others, and we ask our users to do the same. If you believe that content on the Sites infringes your work, or the work of a third party for whom you are authorized to act, please send a notice of the alleged infringement to Mammoth Resorts’ copyright agent including all of the following information, pursuant to the Digital Millennium Copyright Act of 1998 (“DMCA”):

  * An electronic or physical signature of the intellectual property owner, or an agent authorized to act on behalf of the owner;
  * A description of the work that you claim has been infringed, including the URL, website location, or other identifying characteristics;
  * Your name, company name, address, telephone number, fax number, and e-mail address (and, if you are not the owner of the intellectual property, the name of the owner);
  * A statement by you that you have a good-faith belief that the described use of the work is not authorized by the intellectual property owner, its agent, or the law;
  * A statement by you, made under penalty of perjury, that the information in your notice is accurate and that you are either the intellectual property owner or an agent authorized to act on behalf of the intellectual property owner.

Please send the notice of alleged infringement by any of the following:

Attn: General Counsel

U.S. Mail: Mammoth Resorts

PO Box 24

Mammoth Lakes, California 93546

E-mail: [800Mammoth@mammothresorts.com](mailto:800Mammoth@mammothresorts.com)  (please include “attn: General Counsel” in the subject line)

Mammoth Resorts may terminate use of our Sites by repeat infringers in appropriate circumstances pursuant to the DMCA. 

Complaint Policy (including Trademark and Privacy)

If you believe in good faith that any Content, Submission, or other material posted on a Site infringes any of your rights other than in copyright, or is otherwise unlawful, you may send a notice to 800Mammoth@mammoth-mtn.com containing the following information:

  * Your name, physical address, e-mail address and phone number;
  * A description of the Content, Submission, or other material posted on the Site that you believe violates your rights or is otherwise unlawful, and which parts of said materials you believe should be remedied or removed;
  * Identification of the location of the material on the Site;
  * If you believe that the material violates your rights, a statement as to the basis of the rights that you claim are violated;
  * If you believe that the material is unlawful or violates the rights of others, a statement as to the basis of this belief;
  * A statement under penalty of perjury that you have a good faith belief that use of the material in the manner complained of is not authorized and that the information you are providing is accurate to the best of your knowledge and in good faith; and,
  * Your physical or electronic signature. 

If we receive a message that complies with all of these requirements, we will evaluate the submission, and if appropriate, in Mammoth Resorts’ sole discretion, Mammoth Resorts will take action. We may disclose your submission to the poster of the claimed violative material, or any other party.

Registration and Password Protection

You may wish to register on one of our Sites in order to access a service, receive information, make a purchase, enter an online promotion, or for other purposes indicated on various sections of our Sites from time to time. In consideration of your use of the Sites, if you register on any of our Sites, you agree to provide true, accurate, current and complete information about yourself.

Your account, including your username and password, are personal to you and may not be used by anyone else. You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of your password and username and are fully responsible for all activities that occur under your password or username by you or by anyone else using your username and password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately inform us of any apparent breaches of security such as loss, theft or unauthorized disclosure or use of your username or password, and until we are so notified you will remain liable for any unauthorized use of your account.

You may not register on our Sites or open an account if you are under the age of 13. The Sites are not directed to individuals under the age of 13, nor do they contain information which would be potentially harmful to minors in any way.  However, we advise all visitors to the Sites under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any Personally Identifiable Information. In the event that Mammoth Resorts discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personally Identifiable Information to us, we will delete the child's Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, pursuant to 47 U.S.C. Section 230 (d), as amended, we hereby notify you that parental control protections are commercially available to assist you in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors.  More information on the availability of such software can be found through publicly available sources. You may wish to contact your Internet Service Provider for more information.

Please see the Federal Trade Commission's website for this act:  http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/ for more information.

Feedback

We welcome your comments, feedback, suggestions, and other communications regarding these Sites and the information and services we make available through these Sites (collectively, “Feedback”). The Feedback you provide to us through these Sites will become and remain our exclusive property. Your submission of Feedback will constitute an assignment to us of rights, title and interests in your Feedback, including all copyrights and other intellectual property rights in your Feedback. We will be entitled to reduce to practice, exploit, make, use, reproduce, disclose, display or perform publicly, distribute, improve and modify any Feedback you submit.

International Use of Our Sites

Recognizing the global nature of the Internet, you agree to comply with all local rules regarding online conduct and acceptable Content. You assume all knowledge of applicable laws and you are responsible for compliance with any such laws. You may not use the Site in any way that violates applicable state, federal, or international laws, regulations or other government requirements.  Specifically, you agree to comply with all applicable laws regarding the transmission of technical data exported from the United States or the country in which you reside.

Indemnity

You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Mammoth Resorts, its affiliates, assignees, successors-in-interest and its suppliers, and each of their respective partners, employees, representatives and agents, from and against all claims, losses, costs, damages, liabilities and expenses (including, but not limited to, attorney fees) arising out of:

  * Your activities in connection with the Sites; 
  * Any violation of these Terms of Use by you;
  * Any improper or unauthorized use of the Mammoth Resorts Content, User Content, or other content by you;
  * Any conduct, activity or action which is unlawful or illegal under any state, federal or common law, or violative of the rights of any individual or entity, engaged in, caused by, or facilitated in any way through the use of software, services, Mammoth Resorts Content or User Content or any other such service or information which appears on the Site; and,
  * Any allegation that anything you transmit or attempt to transmit, including but not limited to any Mammoth Resorts Content or User Content you submit, post, or otherwise make available, through or in connection with the Site, infringes or otherwise violates the intellectual property, privacy or other rights of any third party.

Third Party Sites

Our Sites may contain links to websites operated by other entities. If you decide to visit any linked site, you do so at your own risk and it is your responsibility to take all protective measures to guard against viruses or other destructive elements. Third party websites are not bound by these Terms of Use or by Mammoth Resorts’ Privacy Policy.

Disclaimer of Warranties

YOUR USE OF THE SITES IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE SITES ARE PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS" AND "AS AVAILABLE" BASIS. MAMMOTH RESORTS EXPRESSLY DISCLAIMS ALL WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO THESE SITES, THEIR CONTENT, THE SOFTWARE, OR ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES DESCRIBED ON OR AVAILABLE ON THE SITES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT. MAMMOTH RESORTS MAKES NO WARRANTY:  THAT THE SITES WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; THAT THE SITES WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE OR THAT THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITES WILL BE ACCURATE OR RELIABLE; THAT THE QUALITY OF ANY PRODUCTS, SERVICES, INFORMATION, OR OTHER MATERIAL PURCHASED OR OBTAINED BY YOU THROUGH THE SITES WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS. ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED THROUGH THE SITES IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK.

Limitation of Liability

TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMITTED BY APPLICABLE LAWS WE, ON BEHALF OF OUR EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, SUPPLIERS, AND CONTRACTORS, EXCLUDE AND DISCLAIM LIABILITY FOR ANY LOSSES AND EXPENSES OF WHATEVER NATURE AND HOWSOEVER ARISING INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO, DAMAGES FOR LOSS OF PROFITS, GOODWILL, USE, DATA OR OTHER INTANGIBLE LOSSES (EVEN IF MAMMOTH RESORTS HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES), ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE USE OF THE SITES OR ANY WEB SITE WITH WHICH THEY ARE LINKED, OR ANY PRODUCTS OR SERVICES AVAILABLE ON THESE SITES, OR OTHERWISE RESULTING FROM: (i) THE USE OR THE INABILITY TO USE THE SITES; (ii) THE COST OF PROCUREMENT OF SUBSTITUTE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES RESULTING FROM ANY GOODS, DATA, INFORMATION OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR OBTAINED OR MESSAGES RECEIVED OR TRANSACTIONS ENTERED INTO THROUGH OR FROM THE SITES; (iii) UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS OR DATA; (iv) STATEMENTS OR CONDUCT OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON THE SITES; OR (v) ANY OTHER MATTER RELATING TO THE SITES. THIS LIMITATION OF LIABILITY APPLIES WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER BASIS.

These Terms of Use give you specific legal rights and you may also have other rights which vary from country to country.  Some jurisdictions do not allow the exclusion of implied warranties, or certain kinds of limitations or exclusions of liability, so the limitations and exclusions set out in these Terms of Use may not apply to you.  Other jurisdictions allow limitations and exclusions subject to certain conditions.  In such a case the limitations and exclusions set out in these Terms of Use shall apply to the fullest extent permitted by the laws of such applicable jurisdictions.  Your statutory rights as a consumer, if any, are not affected by these provisions, and we do not seek to exclude or limit liability for fraudulent misrepresentation.

Terminating Permission to Use Our Sites

You may terminate these Terms of Use at any time by ceasing your use of our Sites, destroying all Mammoth Resorts Content, Software or other intellectual property obtained from any Site and all copies and installations thereof, and deleting any accounts you have established on the Sites.  Mammoth Resorts may terminate these Terms of Use or your access to the Sites (in whole or in part) at any time if you violate these Terms of Use in any way. 

Modifications to Terms of Use

We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these Terms of Use at any time.  Alterations of our Sites in no way affect the Terms of Use themselves. Please check the Terms of Use periodically for changes. Modifications become effective immediately upon being posted on the Site, without further notice to you.  Your continued use of our Sites following the posting of changes to the Terms of Use will mean you accept those changes

Miscellaneous

Unless otherwise specified, the Sites and their contents are provided solely for providing information.  The Sites are controlled and operated by Mammoth Resorts from California.  As such, any dispute arising under the Agreement shall be resolved exclusively by California state or federal courts, applying California law, regardless of principles of conflicts of laws, and, by your use, you waive any jurisdictional, venue or inconvenient forum objections to such courts for purposes of resolving these disputes. If we fail to enforce any provision of these Terms of Use, it will not be considered a waiver of our rights.  If any portion of these Terms of Use is held to be unenforceable, then the remaining clauses and provisions will remain in full force and effect.  Any and all warranties, provisions, rights and obligations of the parties herein described and agreed to be performed subsequent to the termination of this agreement shall survive the termination of this agreement. These Terms of Use, including our Privacy Policy and any Additional Terms, constitute the entire agreement between you and Mammoth Resorts, superseding any prior agreements between you and Mammoth Resorts with regard to your use of the Sites.  All of our rights and obligations under these Terms of Use are freely assignable by us in connection with a merger, acquisitions, or sale of our assets.

**Privacy Policy**

Mammoth Resorts Privacy Policy

Mammoth Mountain Ski Area, LLC, Snow Summit, LLC, and other members of the Mammoth Resorts family of businesses (collectively, “Mammoth Resorts,”) know that you care how information about you is collected and used. We take great pride in the relationships we have developed with our guests and we are committed to treating personal information we obtain from you with care and respect. This Privacy Policy (the “Privacy Policy” or “Policy”) is designed to inform you about our privacy policies and practices. This Privacy Policy is part of the Terms of Use published on our Sites. Click here to review the Terms of Use.

Scope of the Privacy Policy

The Privacy Policy applies to the personal information we collect when you visit any Mammoth Resorts web site where the Privacy Policy is posted (our “Sites”). When we use the term “personal information,” we mean information that identifies a particular individual, such as the individual’s name, postal address, e-mail addresses, and telephone number. When other information (such as consumer preferences or demographic information) is directly associated with personal information, this other information is treated as personal information.

Consent to the Policy

By visiting any of our Sites, you agree to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy, you should not use our Sites.

Territoriality

Regardless of where our servers are located, your personal data will be processed by us in the United States, where data protection and privacy regulations may or may not be to the same level of protection as in other parts of the world.  BY VISITING OUR SITES, YOU UNEQUIVOCALLY AND UNAMBIGUOUSLY CONSENT TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING IN THE UNITED STATES OF ANY PERSONAL AND NON-PERSONAL INFORMATION COLLECTED OR OBTAINED BY MAMMOTH RESORTS THROUGH VOLUNTARY SUBMISSIONS, AND THAT UNITED STATES LAW GOVERNS ANY SUCH COLLECTION AND PROCESSING.

Personal Information We Collect and How We Use It

We collect the following types of personal information through our Sites:

_Information You Actively Provide._

We collect the personal information you actively provide when you use one of our Sites. We use the personal information you provide to deliver the programs, products and services that you request, or to process purchases or reservations you have made on our Sites. For example, we use the information you provide when you make a reservation to reserve the type of room you requested at the hotel or resort you selected. If you join any program we offer, such as a loyalty program, we use your personal information to administer the program. Information you provide to us on our Sites will be stored in an online profile we create for you, to enable us to better meet your needs and understand your preferences.

Depending on your privacy preferences, we may use your personal information to send you promotional messages and special offers, via email, text/SMS, telephone call, and pre-recorded automated telephone message. We also use your personal information for security and fraud prevention purposes; to better understand our guests; to improve our programs, services, and Sites; and to better market and advertise our programs and services.

At some of our Sites, you can submit information about other people. For example, if you order a gift, gift card, or gift certificate online and want to send it directly to the recipient, you must submit the recipient’s name and address. We use this information only to send your gift or provide the service requested. We will not add that person’s information to our mailing lists.

We may combine information you have provided to us on our Sites with information you have provided to us offline, and we may store this information together in your online profile. For example, we may combine data automatically collected when you use your season ski pass at one of our resorts or data you provide to us when you stay at one of our hotels with your online profile. This enables us to better understand and meet your needs when you visit our resorts or other properties.

_Information Provided by Others._

From time to time, we may supplement the information you give us with information from third parties. For example, we may supplement your profile with demographic and preference data or we may correct mailing addresses by using public sources. By supplementing your profile, we are better able to provide product recommendations and special offers that will be of genuine interest to you. We may also use this information to further personalize our Sites and improve your experience while you are on our Sites.

_Information Sent to Us by Your Web Browser._

We collect information that is automatically sent to us by your web browser. This information typically includes your IP address; the name and version of your operating system; the name and version of your browser; the page you were visiting before you accessed our Site; and the date and time of your visit. The information we receive depends on the settings of your browser. Please check your browser if you want to learn what information your browser sends or how to change your settings. Generally, we use this information to create statistics that help us improve our Sites and make them more compatible with the technology used by our visitors. This information is also used for marketing purposes and to improve your experience on the Sites.

We may collect IP addresses for purposes of system administration, to report traffic data to our corporate partners, and to audit the use of our Sites. Although the information provided by your browser does not identify you personally, this data can be combined with other data to personally identify you.

_Cookies._

We also use "cookies" as a method to gain dependable and consistent traffic data. A "cookie" is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to help us provide customizable services and to allow you to sign-in to our Sites. Cookies may also be used by Mammoth Resorts corporate partners on co-branded Web pages. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings of your browser. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience at our Sites and other Web sites may be diminished and some features will not work as intended.

_Advertising Servers._

We may hire other companies to place our banner ads on other websites. Those companies may perform tracking and reporting activities on the ads they serve for us, as well as user reaction. They would not collect any information other than IP addresses and behaviors associated with those IP addresses on our behalf, and we will not give any personal information to them. Third-party advertising servers are subject to their own privacy policies. Our service providers are bound by contract to keep your personal information confidential and use it only to perform services on our behalf.

Disclosure of Your Personal Information

Mammoth Resorts does not sell your personal information to outside marketers or advertisers. Under limited circumstances we may disclose the personal information we collect with outside parties for specific purposes. Those circumstances are described below along with some of the steps we take to limit the manner in which your personal information is used.

We may share your information with companies that provide support services to us (such as credit card processors, mailing houses, web hosts, or providers of online reservation services) or that help us market our products and services (such as email vendors). These companies may need information about you in order to perform their functions. These companies are only authorized to use the personal information we share with them for the purpose of delivering the service we hire them to provide. In addition, we only disclose the information they need to provide the specific service or function. We will not sell your personal information to third party marketing or advertising firms.

Personal information collected on any of the Sites may also be shared with other members of the Mammoth Resorts family of businesses, including current or future parents, affiliates, subsidiaries, and entities sharing common ownership with Mammoth Resorts. All of the Mammoth Resorts entities with whom we share your personal information will be bound to this Privacy Policy.

We may occasionally feature web pages on which you can register for special promotions or services provided in conjunction with our business partners. When we feature pages like these on our Sites, we will give you a clear notice that you are providing information to another party. We may also arrange to send you marketing and promotional information of other reputable companies that we think might be of interest to you, only if you tell us that you want to receive these sorts of materials. We do not share your personal information with these companies.

If some or all of the business assets of one of our companies or Sites are sold or transferred, we generally would transfer the corresponding information regarding our guests and customers to the acquiring business so that they can continue to operate the business, but your information would remain subject to this Policy.

In certain special cases, we may disclose your personal information when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to you, Mammoth Resorts or someone else. We may also disclose your personal information when we believe the law requires it, or in response to any demand by law enforcement authorities in connection with a criminal investigation, or civil or administrative authorities in connection with a pending civil case, administrative investigation or investigation conducted by Mammoth Resorts.

Links to Third-Party Websites

Our Sites contain direct links to sites offered by third parties. Some of these sites are authorized to use Mammoth Resorts brands or logos. Those third-party sites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

Some of the Sites may give you the option of sharing your thoughts, personal information, or skiing and snowboarding experiences automatically on their platforms. If you choose to share information with a third-party site such as Twitter, Facebook, or Instagram, the information you choose to share on those sites is not subject to this Privacy Policy. You should review the privacy policies of those websites to make an informed decision about whether to share your information on those sites. Further, you should review your account settings on those sites to ensure that you are comfortable sharing your information with the audience chosen in that account.

Location Information

From time to time, we may use technology that provides us with information about your geographic location (“location information”). For example, when you ride a chairlift of one of our resorts, we scan or read your ski pass. We read passes through the use of handheld scanners or passive radio frequency readers mounted on or near our chairlifts. This information helps us monitor use of the lifts and tells us when you ride one of our chairlifts. When we collect location data about our guests offline, we may combine that information with personal information that we collect online and use the information to better understand our guests or to provide you with information or services. Location Information collected and combined in that manner is subject to this Privacy Policy.

Children’s Privacy

We will not knowingly collect personal information on our Sites from children under the age of 13 without the prior consent of the child’s parent or guardian. If you believe that a child under the age of 13 may have provided personal information to us without consent of the child’s parent or guardian, please contact us at [800Mammoth@mammothresorts.com](mailto:800Mammoth@mammothresorts.com)

You may not register on our Sites or open an account if you are under the age of 13. The Sites are not directed to individuals under the age of 13, nor do they contain information which would be potentially harmful to minors in any way.  However, we advise all visitors to the Sites under the age of 13 not to disclose or provide any Personally Identifiable Information. In the event that Mammoth Resorts discovers that a child under the age of 13 has provided Personally Identifiable Information to us, we will delete the child's Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, pursuant to 47 U.S.C. Section 230 (d), as amended, we hereby notify you that parental control protections are commercially available to assist you in limiting access to material that is harmful to minors.  More information on the availability of such software can be found through publicly available sources. You may wish to contact your Internet Service Provider for more information.

Please see the Federal Trade Commission's website for this act:  http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/edcams/kidzprivacy/ for more information.

Opting Out 

_Opt-Out of Receiving Future Communications_

Our Sites give you the option of not receiving future communications from us by unsubscribing from our lists at <http://www.mammothmountain.com/winter/home/email-unsubscribe> or by sending an email to 800Mammoth@mammoth-mtn.com

_Review and Update Your Information_

You may also review or update your personal information collected by this Site or correct factual inaccuracies by emailing [800Mammoth@mammothresorts.com](mailto:800Mammoth@mammothresorts.com)

How We Protect Your Information

Mammoth Resorts has appropriate physical, technological, and organizational safeguards and security measures in place to attempt to protect against the loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure of your personal information under our control. However, it is important that you understand that no website or database is completely secure, or “hacker proof.” You can help us by protecting and keeping your passwords safe at all times. You can protect yourself and help us prevent computer crime by promptly notifying us if you suspect that your credit card, pass product with PassCash, user name or password is lost, stolen or used without permission. Also, you can reduce many risks by using up to date antivirus software.

Changes to the Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, by posting the revised Privacy Policy on our Sites. The changes will only apply to the personal information we collect after we have posted the revised Privacy Policy.

We will attempt to notify you of any significant changes to this Privacy Policy by sending an email notice. However, it is your responsibility to check this Site for updates as you will be bound by them if you choose to visit our Sites.

California Privacy Rights

Beginning on January 1, 2005, California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as S.B. 27, or the “Shine the Light” law, allows California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosures in the prior calendar year, if any, of their personally identifiable information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please contact us at 800Mammoth@mammoth-mtn.com with “Request for California Privacy” in the letter subject line. You must include sufficient detail for us to locate your file; at a minimum, your name, email and postal address.

We will attempt to provide you with the requested information within thirty (30) days of receipt. We reserve our right not to respond to requests sent more than once in a calendar year, or requests submitted to an address other than the one posted in this notice. Please note that the California Shine the Light law does not cover all information sharing. Our disclosure only includes information covered by the law.

Visitors Who Access Our Sites From Outside the United States

Our Sites and databases may be hosted on Web servers located in the United States or other countries. We share the personal information we collect with our third-party service providers, and others around the world as described in this Privacy Policy. When we transfer your personal information to another country, we will take appropriate measures to protect your privacy and personal information. By using one of our Sites, you are consenting to the transfer of your personal information to any country in the world in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

The Sites are U.S. Sites and are governed by U.S. law. If you do not wish to consent to U.S. law or this Privacy Policy, you should not share information with us or use our Sites.

Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or the practices of our Sites, please contact:

Mammoth Resorts

PO Box 24

Mammoth Lakes, CA 93546

1-[800-626-6684](tel:800-626-6684)

Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy was updated on March 18, 2015, and is effective as of that date.
